TEN (ENVELOPE)
[narrator] Ten:
The ability to envelop your body
in a shroud of Nen aura,
making it tougher,
and slowing the effects of aging.
ZETSU (SUPPRESS)
Zetsu:
A technique which shuts off
your flow of Nen aura.
Effective for concealing your presence
and recovering from fatigue.
REN (REFINE)
Ren:
A technique for creating
an especially strong Nen aura.
It is crucial for increasing your power.
HATSU (RELEASE)
Hatsu:
The release of your Nen aura,
after using Ren to boost it.
These four elements
are known as the Four Exercises
and are critical to the mastery of Nen.
FOUR EXERCISES
[theme song playing]
[whooshing]
[Zushi] Master?
[Wing] Master...
It was never my intention, but...
have I...
Have I awoken a terrible monster?
DESTINY x AND x TENACITY
[narrator] One month has passed
since Gon was injured
in his fight with Gido.
In Heavens Arena,
all eyes are focused
on a certain upcoming match.
[grunting]
Hey, Gon! I got something--
Oh! Killua!
What’s up? I was just thinking about
going out to look for you.
Whoa! You’re better already?
[Gon] Yeah! [grunts]
Check it out! I’m all good!
Yeah, Okay, I get it.
Those injuries should’ve kept him
out of commission for four months,
but he recovered in one!
What is your body made of anyway?
I really don’t know how to answer that.
You’re such a weirdo.
So... Weren’t you gonna
say something earlier?
Oh. That’s right.
Tickets, huh?
But these aren’t just any tickets.
They’re for Hisoka’s fight.
As a 200th floor level fighter
I got dibs on tickets.
Hisoka’s match is real popular.
I even saw scalpers.
Mmm...
So, I’ve been trying
to gather up information.
Turns out Hisoka’s the real deal.
He has an eight and three record
with six KO’s,
all of which ended in death.
[Gon] Yeah, but he’s lost three matches.
[Killua] His three losses were forfeits.
Forfeits? Really?
Well, he reached
the registration deadline,
so he signed up for a fight,
then didn’t show.
Okay, what does that mean?
That when Hisoka does compete,
he never loses.
Guess so.
And out of all the times he’s fought,
he’s only given up a total of four points.
One of ‘em was a knockdown
and three were clean hits.
Which means he’s gotta be as strong
as any of the Floor Masters.
[Gon] Wow. That’s pretty intimidating...
[trembling with excitement]
[Killua] Damn it.
You sure don’t look
very intimidated to me.
[Killua]
So, his opponent is some guy named Kastro.
Two years ago, he managed to get
the only knockdown ever against Hisoka.
[Gon] Hmm...
Of the four points Hisoka
has ever given up to another fighter,
this Kastro guy is responsible
for three of them.
Three points against Hisoka?
[Killua]
Guess you could say they’ve got history.
They both registered for the same day,
so they could fight each other.
[Gon] Hmmm…
This is your chance.
You’ll get to analyze
Hisoka’s fighting style.
Maybe he’ll even go all-out!
Uh….
Are you sure this is okay?
I made that promise to Mister Wing...
[Wing] I won’t allow you to participate
in any matches for two months.
Nor will I allow the study of
or training in the use of Nen.
Are you kidding?
Of course it’s okay!
You’re just gonna be watching a match.
[both gasp]
Not okay.
Viewing a match counts
as studying the use of Nen.
Uh, Mister Wing!
C’mon, don’t scare us like that!
[Wing gasps] Gon,
has your arm healed up already?
Uh, yes sir! It’s all better now.
[Wing] What incredible regeneration!
Can’t he watch the match
since he recovered and everything?
Oh, no. When I told Gon he had to
wait two months, I meant two months.
[groans]
Now, Gon. You still have another month.
You are to continue to practice Ten
and recover from your injuries.
Um… Right, Mister Wing. I understand.
Well… That’s all, then.
Osu! Take care!
Okay. Well, that’s it.
You’ll just have to watch a recording.
I’ll go see it in person.
Mm.
[Wing] They’ve kept their promise
every day and have only performed Ten.
I can tell from the faint aura
that constantly surrounds them
under normal circumstances.
Their aura flows
like a great but tranquil river.
Master Wing?
[Wing] Hm?
Oh, never mind. It’s nothing, really, sir.
[Wing] This won't do.
It seems I’m the one who’s losing my calm.
[Cocco] Hello! I’m your announcer, Cocco!
Today in Heavens Arena,
we have Kastro versus Hisoka,
-the match you’ve all been waiting for!
-[gasps]
Just take a look at this crowd, folks!
Isn’t it amazing?
[cheering]
The match won’t get started
for another hour,
-but the arena is already packed!
-[remote beeps]
[Wing] This is a promise thread.
Its purpose to remind you
of the promise you made.
[Gon moaning]
[Cocco] Hisoka took home the win
when they faced each other two years ago!
The audience here is obviously fired up
to see this fated rematch unfold
as Kastro looks to take his
long-awaited revenge!
His record is eight wins and three losses,
but only because he failed to show!
Hisoka the magician is the grim reaper
who’s prone to taking days off!
With nine wins after his loss to Hisoka
for a nine-one record,
only one away
from challenging the Floor Masters,
is Kastro!
He’s vowed to get payback.
But will he succeed?
Get ready for an epic battle
between the two fighters
closest to reaching the Floor Masters!
[Killua] Wow. I figured he’d be
all big and muscle-y.
[Cocco] Next up,
we have an interview with Kastro
from a few days ago!
I wouldn't fight
if I didn't expect to win.
You’ll see that in the last two years,
I’ve become a different person.
[Killua] Huh. Sounds confident.
Let’s see if he’s got what it takes
to back that confidence up.
NO TRESPASSING
UNLESS AUTHORIZED
[gasps]
Huh? What the-?!
[Killua] There he is.
-[Kastro] May I help you?
-[gasps]
[Killua] What?!
But... that’s impossible!
He was sitting on that couch
just a second ago.
When did he move?
Did he open the door
and slip around behind me,
all without me noticing?
No! There’s no way!
I never took my eyes off the door
until after I heard him talk.
He never had the chance...
So how...?
Oh! Well, I--
I was just hoping for an autograph.
[Kastro] From me?
Well, that is quite an honor.
-Killua.
-[gasps]
I try to keep tabs on all my rivals
on the 200th floor.
What’s wrong? Isn’t Gon with you today?
Wow, I guess you really
do know everything, huh?
So, are you here to scout out opponents?
No, not really.
I just wanted to get a look at you
up close is all.
Well then, now that you have,
what do you think of me?
You’re pretty damn impressive.
Thank you.
And your Zetsu
was quite impressive as well, Killua.
Oh?
However, you made a mistake.
It would have been wiser
to conceal your presence here.
Aura of your caliber suddenly disappearing
would be enough to give anyone pause.
So, you’ve been keeping tabs on me
ever since I got onto this floor?
[Kastro] Pretty much.
Well, then I want to know...
how did you do that just now?
Unfortunately, I cannot tell you that.
After all, I might have to fight you
one of these days.
Don’t worry ‘bout that.
I don’t really plan
on fighting here anymore.
[Kastro] Is that so?
Because that isn’t what your aura says.
[chuckles] Oh, I’m only joking.
I’ll show you my answer in the match.
I’ll be waiting at the Battle Olympia.
[door creaking]
I’m certain you can get there.
[angrily]
I said I’m not gonna fight, okay?!
[grumbles]
[cheering]
[Cocco] It’s finally time!
The long-awaited rematch
between Hisoka and Kastro has arrived!
I’m grateful, Hisoka.
If not for your initiation,
chances are that I never would have
gotten this strong.
[chuckling]
Who did you say got strong?
[Kastro] Just so you’re aware,
in the nine matches that I’ve had
since my loss to you,
I’ve never once used my full power.
Every one of them was a warm-up
to defeating you.
[referee] Begin!
Here I come!
[roaring]
[grunts]
[gasps]
That was a clean hit!
Kastro has landed
the first strike of the match!
Hmm...
[Killua] What the hell was that?!
Get serious, Hisoka.
[Cocco]
Kastro has landed the first strike!
Hisoka has surrendered the first point,
after failing to evade
Kastro’s light-speed chop!
[grunts]
[Killua] Was that an optical illusion?
I’m not the person I was two years ago.
I won’t go so easily next time.
I think I’ll decide when I get serious,
if you don’t mind.
Then so be it.
But I strongly recommend
that you decide quickly.
[Hisoka grunts]
[audience] Ooh!
[Killua] Again?
I was sure he'd dodge that one, too!
[grunts]
Are you just going to run,
or are you going to fight me?
[Kastro grunts]
[Hisoka grunts]
That’s a clean hit and a knockdown!
[cheering]
[Cocco] What a surprise, folks!
I can hardly believe it!
Kastro has been knocking
his opponent around like a rag doll!
The score is now four-zero, but...
what did I just see?
Was that my imagination?
So, you still won’t change your mind?
Is it really preferable to you
to die in ignorance?
Seems so.
[referee] C--Can you still fight?
-[Hisoka chuckles]
-[referee gasps]
[Hisoka] Am I seeing things?
Because it looked to me
like you just vanished.
[Cocco] That’s right! That’s what it was!
He vanished!
That’s what I saw, too!
No.
‘Vanished’ is close,
but it’s not quite the right word.
You were right in front of me,
preparing to deal a kick,
and then suddenly,
you were behind me.
I’d have to say that comes the closest
to describing what happened.
But something still feels wrong...
out of place.
Yes.
I can’t help but feel as if I’m missing
something very basic here.
This is futile.
You can’t solve anything
if you keep running away from me.
In any case, I’m done waiting.
I’ll take your arm with my next strike.
If you insist on remaining pompous,
be my guest.
I’m beginning to think
that you weren’t meant for anything more.
TIGER BITE FIST
[Kastro growling]
[spectator 1] That’s The Tiger Bite Fist!
[spectator 2] Kastro’s getting serious!
[Killua] Tiger Bite Fist?
Masters can rip whole trees in half
with their hands
using that technique.
Meanwhile, Hisoka still
hasn’t figured out Kastro’s ability.
Then again, neither have I.
At this rate, Hisoka’s dead meat!
Here I come!
[gasps]
Take it already.
[snorts] Is this a trap
or just foolish complacency?
One way or the other, your arm is mine!
This one, that is.
-What the--?!
-Hisoka’s arm is...
Hisoka’s right arm
has been completely severed!
[audience screaming]
If you still think you can get your way,
you are sorely mistaken.
This is all within expectations.
The hell it is! [grunts]
[Cocco] Wow!
Have we ever seen Hisoka
in such a perilous situation before,
folks?
He's taken on some serious damage!
[laughs] Yes, I see.
Now I know exactly what your ability is.
You can create...
a double, right?
Very impressive.
You finally got it.
A double? What’s he talking about?
[gasping in shock]
So, it wasn’t an optical illusion
after all!
When Kastro attacked,
it looked like there was another Kastro
superimposed on top of him!
[Cocco] What in the world
is going on here?!
Am I seeing things
or has Kastro really split in two?
Did he just clone himself?
Kastro went from disappearing
to multiplying!
Did he have a twin all along?
I wonder if this is
what they call a doppelgänger.
[both] Indeed it is.
[Zushi] Did he say a doppelgänger?
[Wing] Yes.
But Master...
What does that mean?
I’ve never heard of it.
It refers to a double
or in other words, an additional you.
When you spot someone
who closely resembles you,
that is called a doppelgänger.
I’m sorry, Master.
I still don’t get it.
Whenever you encounter your doppelgänger,
you begin to experience
headaches and fatigue,
both of which continue
until your double vanishes.
Some people believe
that the double actually siphons energy
away from the original,
prompting these physical reactions.
But Kastro isn’t suffering at all
right now.
He’s way too strong for that!
That’s only a story, Zushi.
It’s clear he mastered this
through intense training.
I did as you advised
and observed you without trying to evade.
And it turns out ‘vanished’
was the right word
for what you’ve been doing all along.
But then,
why couldn’t I shake the feeling
that there was something missing before?
You vanished, yes...
but I still felt your presence by my side.
In fact, just before you vanished,
I felt even more of you.
Before you disappear,
you duplicate yourself.
[both chuckle] I’m impressed
that you managed to figure that out.
Using Nen, I was able to successfully
create a double.
And while my double
goes on the attack for me,
I lurk safely in the shadows.
[both Kastros] As soon as you react...
[Kastro] ...I release my double
and attack myself.
[Killua] So that’s why
he wears those clothes.
The fluttering helps create blind spots.
That’d be hard to figure out
during combat,
even for a skilled Nen user.
[Kastro] You see…
my double is no mere illusion.
It’s real.
Just as real as I am
until I make it vanish.
You must know this.
You felt it strike against you.
To put it simply,
you’re going to have to face
two of me at once!
Now behold the culmination
of my mastery of Nen.
The True Tiger Bite Fist!
[chuckles]
[Cocco] Incredible!
We have an upset in the making!
Hisoka won two years ago,
but now he’s in big trouble!
Is Kastro about to avenge
his only previous defeat?!
And now I will sever your left arm,
if only to see if you can maintain
your appearance of disinterest.
[chuckles] Well, let’s find out...
Maybe I feel more up to it now.
[narrator] Kastro, the fearsome user
of conjured doubles
and Hisoka, the magician.
The end of their battle will be
as incredible as the match itself.
Though Gon knows nothing of this yet.
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we're introducing Riehlvelt,
who uses accumulated aura
to move his wheelchair around.
And he fights with two whips!
Come to think of it,
there’s probably a secret there.
Whip! Whip!
[Gon] Next time: "A x Surprising x Win"!
[Killua] Hey, Gon.
If you could clone yourself,
what would you do?
[Gon]
Play rock-paper-scissors!
[Killua]
Wouldn’t you just tie every time?